Defend the castle!
Hasn't the crown prince escaped yet?
It's not that simple! The princes
are too young to flee swiftly!
In any case, we defend
this place to the death!
Hold until the signal bell rings!
Here is the man who brought about this war,
the emperor of Galkhein:
Arnold Hein.
Here we go!
Sir!
I lived this life to the fullest, too.
But...
Next time... Next time, I'll...
Rishe Irmgard Weitzner!
You are a devious woman unworthy of
being the fiancée of a crown prince!
Today, as of this moment,
I annul my engagement to you!
Very well. I understand.
Huh?
Hold on. I'm voiding our engagement.
You must be worried about
what will happen to you now.
No, not in the least.
What?
If you'll pardon me.
Huh? W-Wait!
Rishe? Where are you going?
Listen to me!
Once again, I've returned.
I spent a whole week thinking about
how I'd read off your list of crimes!
Listen! Hey! You! Come back here!
I already know how I'm to be treated.
Halt! Rishe! Listen to me
when I'm speaking to you!
After all,
this is the seventh time I've relived my life.
Even now, I can recall it clearly...
My very first life.
Rishe Irmgard Weitzner!
You are a devious woman unworthy of
being the fiancée of a crown prince!
Today, as of this moment,
I annul my engagement to you!
Wh-What? You're breaking off our engagement?
But... why?
You will be exiled from this kingdom.
Crown Prince Dietrich...
Do you really mean what you're saying?
I will now list your crimes.
Crimes?!
We are a ducal house, with an
oath of loyalty to the crown.
To think that you, my only daughter,
would betray that oath.
You should be ashamed, Rishe.
They're false accusations!
Please, listen to me!
Father! Mother!
My engagement was broken.
My family abandoned me.
With nothing but the clothes on
my back, I wandered aimlessly.
What do I do now?
Is it fun staring at the ground like that,
young lady?
That's when it happened.
That's when I met that band
of traveling merchants.
You look like you're going
through a rough patch.
This cart is headed to the next
country over. Want a ride?
You sure about this, chief?
You're a real pushover when it
comes to beauties like her.
Are these people merchants?
That's true!
Idiots. I've got a better eye
for people than you think.
Even in the moonlight, that silk
shines with an impressive luster.
It's Vishkulha made, isn't it?
So you're from the royal family,
or maybe a duke's house.
A noble young lady like you
out this late can only—
Excuse me!
Would you buy this ring from me?
We don't just buy and sell things.
We find goods that set our
hearts ablaze—that fire us up—
and we sell them to people who are
just as excited about them as us.
Both buyer and seller love the wares, and
that's what creates the profit in the trade.
That's our creed—the creed
of the Aria Trading Company.
That face... You just thought,
"that sounds like fun," didn't you?
I-I...
Your life's a blank slate right now, isn't it?
Why don't you take this opportunity
to embark on the path of a merchant?
Me? I've never even considered it.
You've been freed from your stifling destiny
as the wife of a crown prince.
You can go anywhere.
You're free to do whatever you want.
Free... to do what I want...
You have a good eye.
And...
You possess the kind of amazing luck that
led you to a friendly caravan like ours!
If you became a merchant, I think
things would get pretty interesting.
How about it? Are you in?
Yes, please! Please teach me
how to be a merchant!
My first life.
I learned how to trade under Chief Tully.
Then I set out on my own as a merchant.
I traveled the world, pursuing my newfound
dream of visiting every country in it.
And then, with just one
country left on my list,
I was swept up in a war...
and ended up losing my life.
What?
Rishe Irmgard Weitzner!
You are a devious woman unworthy of
being the fiancée of a crown prince!
Today, as of this moment,
I annul my engagement to you!
Crown Prince Dietrich?
What is all this?
My dress and ring are just
as they were on that day.
Is this... a dream?
You will be exiled from this kingdom.
It hurts.
Does the dissolution of our engagement
sadden you that much?
If this isn't a dream...
I see. I see.
then I don't have a moment to lose!
Soon, they'll lock me out of the mansion!
If you'll pardon me.
Huh? W-Wait!
Rishe? Where are you going?
Listen to me!
Thank you, gods!
I spent a whole week thinking about
how I'd read off your list of crimes!
I don't understand how,
but I've been given a second chance at life!
Listen! Hey! You! Come back here!
The only regret I harbored about that night...
was that I wasn't able to bring
more of my personal effects with me.
If I'd had more seed money as a merchant,
I would have been able to grow
my enterprise more quickly.
Now I just need to meet Chief Tully and
everyone from the Aria Trading Company again!
But by the time I arrived, the Company's
carts had already passed through.
It can't be. Is this because I went
back home and gathered my things?
The Pictorial Herbal of Foreign Medicinal
Plants my grandmother left me...
Unlike last time, I have money.
In which case, I just need to
decide what to do with it.
In my second life, I sold my possessions,
used the proceeds to cross the sea,
and chose to study medicine.
With information on where
medicinal plants grew,
and the knowledge of when
epidemics would spread,
I was able to put the experience
I'd gained from my first life to good use.
One day, I traveled to a kingdom in the north
and saved a sickly prince.
Your complexion is looking much better, Kyle.
Thank you, Weitzner.
I feel so well today that
I even surprise myself.
It's all thanks to your medicine.
I'm so glad.
My life as an herbalist was fulfilling
and incredibly rewarding.
But once again in my second life,
just as I'd been in my first...
I was swept up in a war and died.
Rishe Irmgard Weitzner!
You are a devious woman unworthy of
being the fiancée of a crown prince!
Today, as of this moment,
I annul my engagement to—
I understand and comply.
Understand what?!
For my third life, I set my
sights on something else:
a specialized branch of study that
I'd learned of in my previous life,
and a genius scholar who specialized in it.
For me, his was the familiar face of
an acquaintance from my second life,
Doctor Michel Evan.
No matter how perfect you
believe your theory to be,
it is only through repeated experimentation
that you may draw a valid conclusion.
Yes, Doctor!
You really do seem to enjoy your research.
Learning new things is so very exciting!
It expands my horizons,
and causes me to view even yesterday's
sights in a whole new light!
After that, the good doctor and I parted ways,
and as I continued my research alone,
once again...
I was swept up in a war and died.
From serving as a handmaid in a
duke's household in my fourth life,
to disguising myself as a man
and fighting as a knight in my sixth life...
In each life, I found a sense of fulfillment,
and I enjoyed them all very much.
But...
In each new life of mine,
once five years have passed,
I die without fail.
Even when I didn't die from
being swept up in the war,
I spent my days so busy
I nearly died from overwork!
And now, I find myself reliving
my life for the seventh time.
I want to spend this go-around taking it easy.
And more than anything else,
I swear I'll live a long life this time!
Now that I think about it,
up until this point, I've always
left through the main entrance.
But as I am now, this way will be quicker—
I'm so very... sorry...
You certainly charged around that corner—
Emperor Arnold Hein!
You know who I am?
This is the first time
I've come to this kingdom.
My name is Rishe Imgard Weitzner.
Though this is the first time we have met,
I must say that your reputation precedes you.
Just now, you called me
"emperor," didn't you?
As my father, the emperor, still lives,
I am no more than a crown prince. And yet...
Well...
My deepest apologies, Your Royal Highness.
In my flustered state, it seems
I misspoke most disrespectfully.
However, my engagement has presently
been annulled, so I am in no small hurry.
I must take my leave now.
A broken engagement?
Wait.
There.
Has something happened?
Oliver, ready my horse.
As you command.
What are you planning to do?
This body has far too little endurance.
I'll have to train all over again.
What?
I've spent a week planning it—my masterpiece!
Prince Dietrich! It's Lady Rishe!
What?
Out of the way! You, let me pass!
You took your time, Rishe.
You don't wish to hear your beloved,
me, speak more words of
condemnation. I understand.
However, it won't go as you wish.
Bringing the hammer of justice down
upon wicked women such as you
is one of my duties as the
future king of this land!
Not only did I fail to make it in time,
this is the absolute worst
timing of any of my lives.
If only I'd arrived later
than in my first life,
I might have avoided seeing his face again.
What are you mumbling about?
It's just as I thought.
At the soirée, you reacted
indifferently to my proclamation,
but it seems to me that you
are deeply saddened at heart.
Pardon?
My annulment of the engagement has you in
such despair that you don't know what to do.
You've been walking, wandering, heartbroken.
I can tell that much with a single glance!
Your dress is covered in mud,
and you have wounds all over your body.
To think that the grief of an engagement
broken reduced you to such a state—
Are you stupid?
What?
Grief does not dirty a dress.
More importantly, I am not sad that
you have broken our engagement.
Wh-What?!
Has the crown prince been
spurned by Lady Rishe?
But Lady Rishe wasn't the one
who broke the engagement, was she?
Still, the crown prince looks
more hurt than she does to me.
You're right!
You there! You're being disrespectful!
The nerve of you peasants!
I am truly glad I did not have to spend
any of my lives married to this person.
Your Royal Highness, you are meant
to protect and cherish your people.
You mustn't speak like you just did.
You are the one who needs
to correct their demeanor.
Don't you have any intention
of asking for my forgiveness?
No. Not the slightest.
In fact, I'm filled with gratitude
to you for breaking our engagement.
What?!
Don't laugh at me!
That's right! You're so mean, Lady Rishe!
Please, don't hurt my precious Prince
Dietrich any more than you already have!
Lady Marie?
Rishe, you bullied my darling
Marie and made her cry, didn't you?
I've heard all about it!
Did you think that a woman as
twisted as you could become queen?
Please, rest at ease.
I will obey your decree regarding
our broken engagement.
I will never again show
myself before either of you.
What?!
Ever since I was a child, I believed that
my position as fiancée to the crown prince
was all that gave my life worth.
But I was mistaken.
I can find my worth myself.
Now that I know that, I have all I need.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I do not require your presence in my life.
Prince Dietrich!
You're so mean, Lady Rishe!
Lady Marie.
Whatever lies you may tell to frame me,
I hold no anger toward you.
Your marriage to His Royal Highness
is for your family's sake, isn't it?
How do you know that?
But please don't forget.
If your future isn't one you wish for yourself,
then there isn't any point to it.
One I wish for?
Finding happiness for your family,
and finding happiness for yourself...
You should be able to do both at once.
Please lead a life where both you
and your family can keep smiling.
Now, the nuisance will remove herself.
Lady Rishe!
All I have is the clothes on my back,
just as I did in my first life.
Stop, Rishe!
Hey, knights! Apprehend Rishe!
Now, where shall I go from here?
Sir!
Um, Lady Rishe? If you could
wait for just a moment...
As I thought. It seems you're
quite the sword master.
Where did you learn those sword skills?
Arnold Hein.
It's a secret.
And my skills are not so great as
to be deserving of praise from you.
You were holding back with
that strike, weren't you?
Hey, who are you? Get away from Rishe!
Everyone, remain as you are!
We mustn't move aggressively against
the crown prince of Galkhein.
The crown prince of Galkhein?!
The beast of a prince said to have single-
handedly annihilated a troop of knights?
Stop that! You'll be killed, too!
Prince Arnold, may I ask
what brings you here?
I assume you didn't draw
your sword just for sport.
That's right.
My sixth life ended at the hands of this man.
One day, he will cause a war
that will envelop the whole world.
The war that causes my death.
What?
What are you doing?
I apologize for my sudden discourtesy.
I have something I wish to ask of you.
Would you please...
do me the honor of becoming my wife?
What?